celoxis.com 2017-06-06

# Celoxis: Privacy Policy

**

#### 1\. INTRODUCTION:

**

We, **Celoxis Technologies Pvt. Ltd. ("Celoxis"; "we"; "our"; "us")** , respect the privacy of everyone who accesses or uses the sites, microsites, mobile application owned, operated and managed by us (" **Website** ") and are committed to protect your (" **Users** "; " **Members** ") data. This privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") describes the procedures we adhere to for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. We recommend you to read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our approach towards the use of your Personal Information (as defined below), while providing the Services to you. By agreeing to access or use the Website and by submitting your Personal Information, you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that those capitalized terms not defined herein, shall have the same meaning ascribed to them in the Terms of Use.

**

#### 2\. STORED PERSONAL INFORMATION:

**

Through the Website, we may collect your Personal Information, including but not limited to your name, and address and IP address (" **Personal Information** "). The Personal Information may also include your phone number, billing information, email address and business postal addresses. You should know that we use the Personal Information for the purposes of our business, for providing you with the Services of our project management software, Celoxis that is offered through the Website (" **Services** ") or for providing you with our newsletters. You shall be solely responsible for the Personal Information shared by you on or to the Website or otherwise to us, including without limitation for its truthfulness and accuracy.

**

#### 3\. STATUTORY PROVISION:

**

This Privacy Policy is governed by and is compliant with **the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules 2011** , (which is designed to protect Personal Information of the users of the Website); and other applicable rules and regulations related to privacy.

**

#### 4\. HOW WE USE PERSONAL AND NON PERSONAL INFORMATION:

**

The Personal Information we collect is used by us to:

  * provide, manage and improve the Services made available to you;
  * create and manage User Accounts;
  * ascertain individual User Accounts at times for resolving any problem or issue or if violation of Terms of Use or Privacy Policy is suspected in relation to the Website
  * manage our relationship with you;
  * to contact you about important announcements and other important things about your User Account.

You understand and acknowledge that in order to provide better Services, we may either directly or through a trusted third party identify the patterns of usage of the Website and/or the Services by the users, with the help of analytical tools developed either by us or by such any third party service providers.

**

#### 5\. COOKIES:

**

We may set " **cookies** " on your use of the Website. If you are a Member of our Website, our Website uses cookies to save your username. Cookies are small encrypted files, that a site or its service provider transfer to your device’s hard drive through your web browser that enables the sites or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

**

#### 6\. DISCLOSURES:

**

We do not sell, rent, lease your Personal Information to anybody and will never do so. We shall not view, share, distribute, print or refer any of your Personal Information, except as provided in the Celoxis Terms of Use, or as may be required by law. Keeping this in mind, we may disclose your Personal Information in the following cases:

  * **Affiliates**. We may provide Personal Information we collect to our affiliates. For example, we may disclose Personal Information to our affiliates in order to respond to your requests for information or Services, or to help limit your receipt of marketing materials you have requested not to receive.
  * **Service Providers or Business Partners**. We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyse, and improve the Services including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service's features. These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. We may disclose your Personal Information to service providers who perform business functions or hosting services on our behalf, who may be located anywhere in the world.
  * **Persons Who Acquire Our Assets or Business**. If we sell or transfer any of our business or assets, certain Personal Information may be a part of that sale or transfer. In the event of such a sale or transfer, we will notify you.
  * **Legal and Regulatory Authorities**. We may be required to disclose your Personal Information due to legal or regulatory requirements. In such instances, we reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required in order to comply with our legal obligations, including but not limited to complying with court orders, warrants, or discovery requests. We may also disclose Personal Information about our Members to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce this Privacy Policy; respond to claims that any Personal Information violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Celoxis, our Members or the general public. You agree and acknowledge that we may not inform you prior to or after disclosures made according to this section.

**

#### 7\. DATA RETENTION:

**

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your registration with us is valid. We may also retain and use your Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your Personal Information within six (06) months upon reasonable written request from you. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting Personal Information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion.

**

#### 8\. SECURITY:

**

We value your Personal Information, and protect it on our Website against loss, misuse or alteration by taking extensive security measures. In order to protect your Personal Information we have implemented adequate technology and will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate. All Personal Information is securely stored in a database, in India and USA.

Although we provide appropriate firewalls and protections, we cannot warrant the security of any Personal Information transmitted as our systems are not hack proof. You understand that the Website and the Services may not be interruption free. We do not provide any guarantee whatsoever with respect to the continuous access to the Website and the Services. Data pilferage due to unauthorized hacking, virus attacks, technical issues is possible and we take no liabilities or responsibilities for it. You are responsible for all actions of your user account and password. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your password to any third party. If you choose to share your user account and password or any Personal Information with third parties, you are solely responsible for the same. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your Personal Information and may be subject to legally binding actions. If you feel that your User Account has been compromised or that there is a potential security flaw within our Website, please contact us as indicated at the end of the page immediately.

**

#### 9\. ACCESSING AND MODIFYING PERSONAL INFORMATION:

**

In case you need to access, remove, review, and/or make changes to the Personal Information that you have provided to us, you may intimate us through an email regarding the same. You can contact us on as indicated at the end of the page.

We may also send you any legally required notifications and certain notifications, including but not limited to, Service related notices or notices regarding a change to any of our policies. For example, we may send you a notice regarding server problems or scheduled maintenance to the Website.

**

#### 10\. THIRD PARTY LINKS AND ADVERTISEMENTS:

**

We may have links to other websites and advertisements on our Website. We shall not be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites. Such links and advertisements are subject to their respective terms of use and any additional guidelines and privacy information provided in relation to that use on their website.

**

#### 11\. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY:

**

You expressly understand and agree that Celoxis shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data, information, details or other intangible losses (even if Celoxis has been advised of the possibility of such damages), resulting from: 

  * the use or the inability to use the Services offered by Celoxis;
  * unauthorized access to or alteration of your Personal Information.

Notwithstanding anything contained in this Privacy Policy or elsewhere, the liability of Celoxis on any account shall not exceed USD 100.

**

#### 12\. GOVERNING LAWS AND DISPUTES:

**

**Governing Laws**. This Agreement shall be construed and governed by the laws of India without regard to principles of conflict of laws.

**Dispute Resolution**. Any dispute arising, between you and Celoxis shall be submitted to the arbitration to be conducted in Pune, India in English language, in accordance with the Rules of Arbitration and Conciliation, of the Bombay Chamber of Commerce and Industry by a sole arbitrator, who shall be appointed by the Administrator of Bombay Chamber of Commerce and the award made in pursuance thereof shall be binding on the parties. The dispute resolution and arbitration process mentioned in this Section will not prohibit parties from approaching the courts for appropriate interim reliefs. Parties further agree that the courts in Pune, India shall have an exclusive jurisdiction over such disputes.

**

#### 13\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY:

**

We may update this Privacy Policy with or without notice to you. You are encouraged to check our Privacy Policy on a regular basis to be aware of the changes made to it.

This Privacy Policy was last modified in July, 2015.

**

#### 14\. CONTACT US:

**

If you have questions or concerns or grievances regarding this Privacy Policy you can email Celoxis’ grievance email-id at [info@celoxis.com](mailto:training@celoxis.com).
